Guide to the Division of Student and Academic Services records, 1987-2009.
Division of Student and Academic Services records
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1993 - 1994 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1993 - 1994 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1993 - 1994 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1994 - 1995 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1994 - 1995 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1994 - 1995 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1995 - 1996 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1995 - 1996 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1995 - 1996 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1996 - 1997 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1996 - 1997 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1996 - 1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Committee on Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1997 - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- Committee on Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1997 - 19982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Committee on Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1997 - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Task Force on Student Activity Fee (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Task Force on Student Activity Fee (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Task force on Student Activity Fee (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Task Force on Admissions and Financial Aid, 1997 - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Task Force on Admissions and Financial Aid, 1997 - 1998 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Committee on Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Committee on Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Committee on Academic Affairs and Campus Life, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- AA and CL, 1999 - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- AA and CL, 1999 - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- TFRC, 1996 - 1997 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- TFRC, 1997 - 1998 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- TFRC, 1998 - 1999 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- TFRC, 1999 - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- TFRC, 2000 - 2001 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Task Force on Athletics (Background/binder) (Box 17, Folder 8)
- TF on Athletics, 1998 - 1999 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- TF on Athletics, 1999 - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- TF on Athletics, 2000 - 2001 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Year 2000 Compliance (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 1995 - 2001 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Student and Academic Services Divisional and Other Meeting Agendas, 1996 - 2000 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- SAS Leadership Communications Audit, 1997 - 1998 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- SAS Training Needs Assessment, 1997 - 1998 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Victims Advocacy Project, 1993 -2003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Fees Charged to Students (Study) (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Student Stress (Ford Study, CALS Work, BOT Request), 1994 - 1998 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Slope Day, 1997 - 1999 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Ivy Council of Presidents, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Ivy Ad Hoc Admissions Group (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Ivy Future Survey (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Ivy Policy Committee, July 1997 - December 1997 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Ivy Policy Committee, January 1998 - June 1998 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Ivy Policy Committee, July 1998 - December 1998 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Ivy Policy Committee, January 1999 - June 1999 (Box 18, Folder 11)
- Ivy Policy Committee, July 1999 - December 1999 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Ivy Policy Committee, January 2000 - June 2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Ivy Policy Committee, July 2000 - December 2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Proposal for the Establishment of a Hispanic Studies Program at CU, 1986 - 1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Barcelo Report (Free Speech), 1987 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- LGB Resource Office Review, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Ivy Policy Committee, January 2001 - June 2001 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Associate Deans, 1996 - 1997 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Associate Deans, 1997 - 1998 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Associate Deans, 1998 - 1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Associate Deans, 1999 - 2000 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Associate Deans, 2000 - 2001 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- CURW/Hillel Addition, 1994 - September 1996 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- CURW/Hillel Addition, October 1996 - 2002 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Creation of Freshman Resource Center, 2000 - 2003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- NCAA Certification, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Sports Club Facility and Field Use Report, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Squash Campaign, 1997 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Athletics and Physical Education Facilities Long Range Plan, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- NCAA Football Review, 1997 - 1998 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- FACAPE Admission Review and Task Force on Athletics, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Robinson Fund, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Athletics and PE Restructuring, July 1996 - February 1996 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Athletics and PE Restructuring, February 1996 - December 1997 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- ECAC, 1987 - 1990 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Emergency Management Planning Team (EMPT) (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Greek Leadership (MGLC, IFC, Panhellenic Assn) (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Sphinx Head (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Kosher Dining Hall - Cohen Trust, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Kosher Dining/Center for Jewish Living Meeting Notes, Spring 1999 - Summer 2001 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 2001 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1994 - 1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1992 - 1993 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1990 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1989 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1988 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- National Council of Young Israel/Center for Jewish Living/Kosher Dining Hall, 1985 - 1987 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- HOST Communications, 1990-1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- HOST Communications, 1997-2001 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Athletics Audits, 1994-2000 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- AAD Donor Group, 1996-1998 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- AAD Donor Group (Box 21, Folder 5)
- ECAC, 2001-2004 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- NCAA Correspondence, 1995-1999 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Residential Communities, 1997-1998 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Residential Initiative Master Plan (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- North Campus Residential Initiative Financial Modeling (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 1999 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2000 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2005 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2007 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2008 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Residential Initiative Executive Group, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Noyes Community Recreation Center (Box 22, Folder 16)
- WCPG (West Campus Planning Group), 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- WCPG, 1999 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- WCPG, 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- WCPG, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- WCP (West Campus Planning), 2001 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- WCP, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- WC Council, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- WC Council Chairs Lunch (Box 23, Folder 8)
- WC Council, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- WC Council, 2006 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- WC Council, 2009 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Donor Materials, 1996-1998 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Donor Materials, 1998-1999 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Donor Materials, 1999-2000 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Donor Materials, 2000-2002 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Budget - Campus Life Operating Plans, 1978-1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Budget - Campus Life and Campus Affairs, 1985-1986 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Report: Cornell and Companies with Investments in South Africa, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- General Plan for Office of Academic Programs, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Division of Campus Life Operating Plan, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Budget Information, including Campus Life Operating Plan, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Document for Division of Campus Life (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Residential Initiative Status Reports (RI Status Reports), 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- RI Status Reports, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- RI Status Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- RI Biannual Status Reports, 2002-2006 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- RI Elastic Resources (Box 24, Folder 12)
- RI Fund Raising (Box 24, Folder 13)
- (Fund for the Improvement of Post Secondary Education) FIPSE Project Challenge, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- FIPSE Project Challenge, 1996-2003 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Harvard Alcohol Study, 1992-1997 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Harvard Alcohol Study, 1998-1999 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Harvard Alcohol Study, 2000-2001 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Harvard Alcohol Study, 2002-2007 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- CSPI (Center for Science in the Public Interest), 1996-1997 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- CSPI, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- CSPI, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- CSPI, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- CSPI, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- CSPI, 1999-2001 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- CSPI Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Board of Trustees, 1996-2003 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- AA and CL (Academic Affairs and Campus Life) Subcommittee on Research, 1999-2002 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- AA and CL, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- TFRC (Task Force on Residential Communities, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- TFRC, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- TFRC, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- TFRC, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- AA and CL, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- AA and CL, 2001-2002 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- AA and CL, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- AA and CL, 2002-2003 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- AA and CL, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- AA and CL, 2003-2004 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- AA and CL, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- AA and CL, 2004-2005 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- President's Council on Cornell Women - Involvement with SAS, 1994-1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Associate Deans, 2002-2004 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Associate Deans, 2005-2006 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- LGBT Program Review Final Report, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- LGBT Resource Center Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- LGBT Resource Center, 2000-2004 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 2000-2001 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 2001-2002 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 2002-2003 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 2003-2004 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 2004-2005 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Student and Academic Services Annual Reports, 2005-2006 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Student and Academic Services, 2000-2003 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- SAS Strategic Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- SAS Strategic Planning, 2001-2002 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- SAS Strategic Planning, 2002-2003 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Student Services Workforce Planning, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Student Services Workforce Planning, 2003 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Miscellaneous Correspondence, 2001-2003 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Student Problems-C.W., 1987-1988 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Student Problems-S.K., 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Student Problems-B.S.L., 1993-1994 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Student Problems-75 Reasons email, 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Student Problems-S.K., 1995-1996 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Student Problems-Racial Tensions, 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Student Problems-B.H., 1996-1997 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Student Problems-C.G., 1997-1998 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Student Problems-C.G., 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Harassment/Lighting, 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Student Problems-S.L., 1998-1999 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Student Problems-S.L., 1999-2000 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Student Problems-Z.B., 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Student Problems-H.M., 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Student Problems-H.M., 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Student Problems-Environmental Issues (Kyoto), 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Student Problems-Bias Incidents (Asian Students and Others), 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Student Problems-Bias Incidents (Asian Students and Others), 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Student Problems-Lambda Upsilon Lambda (Cortez), 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Student Problems-J.A., 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Student Problems-J.A., 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Conflict of Interest Statements, 1999-2000 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Conflict of Interest Statements, 2001-2002 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Conflict of Interest Statements, 2002-2003 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Task Force on Hazing, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Correspondence (Game of Life Filed Here), 2001-2005 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- CF and PC/B and P/PARs, 1997-1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Alumni Fields, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Sailing/Marina (Merrill here) Inlet, 1998-2003 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Sailing/Marina (Merrill here) Inlet, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Lynah Rink Project, 2003-2004 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Title IX/NCAA EADA Data, 1996-2003 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Title IX Review, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Ivy Eligibility, 2001-2002 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- Ivy Eligibility, 2002-2003 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Athletics Alumni Affairs and Development, 1996-2007 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- Alumni Affairs and Development-Donor Group, 1999-2007 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Athletics Campaign, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Athletics Campaign, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Athletics Admissions, 1999-2002 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- NCAA Certification, 1993-1998 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- NCAA Certification, 1999-2006 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Fire Safety Issues, 1997-2001 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- CF and PC/B and P/PARs, 1997-1999 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Advisory Council, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Chapter Services, 2002-2004 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- F and S Housing Policy/Operating and Management Agreement/Tax Implications, 1992-2005 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Rugby, 1995-2003 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Book Project, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- FYE Executive Committee, 2002-2006 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- New York Campus Compact, 1999-2002 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- New York Campus Compact, 2002-2005 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Kaplan Family Program, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Urban Scholars/Heckscher Foundation, 2002-2003 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- UHS Correspondence, 1996-2003 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Graduate Student Health Insurance Repatriation, 1997 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- President's Council on AOD, 2001-2003 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- AOD Policies/Data, 1993-2004 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- AOD Slope Day, 2001-2003 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- CMHW, 2002-2004 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Student Disability Services, 1996-2005 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- PSP General, 2001-2005 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Cornell Commitment, 2002-2005 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- National Student Loan Clearinghouse, 1994-1996 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Admissions, 1997-2001 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Access to College Education, 1998-2004 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Admissions, 2002-2003 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Admissions, 2003-2004 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Middle States Reaccreditation Reports, 1991-2001 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Middle States Reaccreditation Reports, 1999-2004 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Academic Leadership Series, 1998-2001 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Institutional Research and Planning, 2000-2002 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- University Libraries, 1999-2002 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Office of Distance Learning (e-Cornell), 1997-2001 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- New York Science Education Program, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Dragon Day, 1991-2003 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Veterinary Medicine, 1998-2002 (Box 32, Folder 16)